<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<FrameLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:id="@+id/standard_bottom_sheet"
    style="@style/Widget.Material3.BottomSheet.Modal"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    app:layout_behavior="com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior">

    <com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetDragHandleView
        android:id="@+id/drag_handle"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content" />

    <androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="16dp">

        <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content">

            <com.classic.common.MultipleStatusView
                android:id="@+id/multipleStatusView"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:minHeight="150dp"
                app:emptyView="@layout/empty_view"
                app:errorView="@layout/error_view"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
                app:loadingView="@layout/loading_view"
                app:noNetworkView="@layout/no_network_view">

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView_foodHeat_detail"
                    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_margin="16dp"
                    android:text="这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，这是测试数据，" />
            </com.classic.common.MultipleStatusView>
        </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
    </androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>
</FrameLayout>
